Finding Aid for the Alfred Leland Crabb Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Peabody Reflector Extracts, (1930-1970)
  - Editorials Peabody Reflector, (1949-1960) (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Editorials Peabody Reflector, (1949-1960) (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Editorials Peabody Reflector, (1961-1966) (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Editorials Peabody Reflector, (1967-1970) (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Editorials Peabody Reflector, (1938-1948) (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Editorials Peabody Reflector, (1932-1937) (Box 58, Folder 12)
- Personalities of Interest (1)
  - Homes of the Nine Southern Presidents of America (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Elizabeth Page And James Still (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Arthur White Field Spalding, Elizabeth Spencer (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Max Steel (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Henry Timrod, Virginia Lynne Tunstall (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Thomas Mrs. Ruth Arkansas, Laura Thornborough (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Hudson Strode, John Tabb Banister, Robert Tallant (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Jesse Stuart (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Thomas Stribling, James Street, Albert Leeds Stillman (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - John Andrew Rice (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Katherine Ann Porter (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Byron Herbert Reece, Alice Hegan Rice and Lizette Wood Reese (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Robert Ramsey, Clayton Rand and Arthur Papers. (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Writings by Others: Emily Hemeter (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Writings by Others: The Language Of John Crow Ransoms Poetry (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Writings by Others: Southern Artists (Box 59, Folder 16)
- Personalities of Interest (2)
  - Anderson .M .Scruggs, George Scarborough, Evelyn Scott, Robert Rylee (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Harry Harrison Kroll, Harnett T. Kate (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Justus May, James Weldon Johnson, Virgil Carrington Jones (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Zora Neal Hurston, George Pullen Jackson, Beatrice Jefferson (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Stanley Horn, Langston Hughes, Margaret Bell Houston (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Paul Green (The Lost Colony) (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - A. B. Bud Guthrie, Jr, John Gunther, Ross Hilton, Judge Joseph Guild (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Elizabeth Janet Gray, John Temple Graves, Graham Walworth, Frances Gaither (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Douglas Southall Freeman, Adelaide Fries, John Gould Fletcher, Charles Finger (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Augusta Jane Evans, Frances Eisenberg, Dr. W. S. Ellington, Edwin. R. Embree (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Willie Snow Ethridge, Allan Dwight, J. Blunt Clopton (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - W. E. Burghardt Dubois, Will Allen Dromgoole, Clifford Dowdey (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - George Dillon, Frank Dobie, Florence. L .Dorsey (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Josephus Daniels, Jonathan Daniels, Virginius Dabney (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Viola Goode Liddell, Lawrence Lee, Muna Lee, Harry Lee (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - Eloise Liddon & Sarah Litsey (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Augustus Baldwin Longstreet, 1970-1870 (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Randall Jarrell & Paul Green (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - Stark Young & Robert Loveman (Box 60, Folder 19)
  - Donald Davidson (Box 60, Folder 20)
  - Ellen Glasgow (Box 60, Folder 21)
  - Evelyn Hanna, Harris Bernice Kelly, W. C. Handy (Box 60, Folder 22)
  - Daniel Whitehead Hicky, Dubose Heyward, Cecil Fletcher Holland (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - Mildred Haun, William Shakespeare Hays, Legrand Henderson (Box 60, Folder 24)
  - George W. Harris, Corra May Harris, Joel Chandler Harris (Box 60, Folder 25)
- Personalities of Interest (3)
  - Thomasine Cobb McGhee (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Carson McCullers (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Martha McBride Morel (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - David Morton (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Frederick H Koch, Richard Kirk, Wallace McElroy Kelly (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Joseph Wood Krutch (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Lanham Edwin (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Sidney Lanier, Vivian Yeiser Laramore, Clarence John Laughlin, C.P. Lee (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Brainard Cheney, Wilbur Cash, Willa Cather, Madison Cowein (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Mary Bayard Clark, Irvin. S. Cobb, Chris Thomas, P. P. Claxton (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Joseph Cotter, David. L. Cohn (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - James .M. Cain, Jane Todd Crawford, Grace Nell Crowell (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Biographies Of Southern Writers (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Edwin Mims (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Merrill Moore (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Albert Pike & Edgar Allan Poe (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - Felix Glynn Phillips (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - James Robert Perry & Maxwell Perkins (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - Elizabeth Peck & Florence Glass Palmer (Box 61, Folder 19)
  - Bob Porterfield (Box 61, Folder 20)
  - Josephine Pinckney (Box 61, Folder 21)
  - Julia Mood Peterkin (Box 61, Folder 22)
  - Howard Odum & William Alexander Henry (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - E. P O’Donnell (Box 61, Folder 24)
  - Herman Clarence Nixon (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - John Jacob Niles (Box 61, Folder 26)
  - Thomas Holley Chivers (Box 61, Folder 27)
- Personalities of Interest (4)
  - Lilian. E. Smith (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Letters (Crabb) (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Baptistic Influences (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Charlie May Simon, Hubert Standish Skidmore, Sloop Mary Martin, 1951 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Alfred Leland Crabb (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Eric. P. Kelly (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Allen Tate (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Caroline Gordon (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Medora Field (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Gladys Blake, Don Blanding (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Bateman Florence Golson, Roy. P. Basler, Karle Wilson Baker, Bailey Douglas Fields (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Barbara Tunnell Anderson, Allsopp Frederick William, Hervey Allen, James Lane Allen, Conrad Aiken (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Ralph Bates, Katherine Bellman, ED Bell, Joy Bayes (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Blythe Legette, Anna Bontemps, Roark Bradford, Glen Bristow (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - John Mason Brown, Ben Lucien Barman, Charles. F. Bryan (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Dr. Carter Rosalie, Marie Campbell, Carl Cramer (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - George Washington Carver (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Hooding Carter (Box 62, Folder 18)
- Personalities of Interest (5)
  - (Box 63, Folder 1)
- Program Appearances A. L. Crabb, (1920-1947)
  - Program Appearances, (1920-1929) (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Program Appearances, (1930-1934) I (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Program Appearances, (1930-1934) II (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Program Appearances, (1935-1939) I (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Program Appearances, (1935-1939) II (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Program Appearances, (1940-1941) (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Program Appearances, (1942) (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Program Appearances, (1943-1944) (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Program Appearances, (1945-1947) (Box 64, Folder 9)
- Program Appearances A. L. Crabb, (1948-1959)
  - Program Appearances, (1948-1949) (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Program Appearances, (1951-1952) (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Program Appearances, (1953-1954) (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Program Appearances, (1955-1956) (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Program Appearances, (1957-1959) (Box 65, Folder 5)
- Program Appearances A. L. Crabb, (1960-1979)
  - Program Appearances, (1960-1969) I (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Program Appearances, (1960-1969) II (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Program Appearances, (1970-1979) (Box 66, Folder 3)
- Newspaper Clippings On A. L. Crabb, (1940-1949)
  - Newspaper extracts on Crabb, (1940-49) (1) (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper extracts on Crabb, (1940-49) (2) (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper extracts on Crabb, (1940-49) (3) (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper extracts on Crabb, (1950-59) (1) (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper extracts on Crabb, (1950-59) (2) (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper extracts on Crabb, (1950-59) (3) (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper extracts on Crabb, (1960-69) (1) (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper extracts on Crabb, (1960-69) (2) (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper extracts on Crabb, (1970-79) (3) (Box 67, Folder 9)
- News Articles On A. L. Crabb, (1930-1972)
  - News articles on Crabb, (1930-1939) (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - News articles on Crabb, (1940-1942) (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - News articles on Crabb, (1943) (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - News articles on Crabb, (1944-1949) (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - News articles on Crabb, (1950-1955) (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - News articles on Crabb, (1956-1959) (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - News articles on Crabb, (1960-1961) (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - News articles on Crabb, (1962) (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - News articles on Crabb, (1963) (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - News articles on Crabb, (1964-1966) (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - News articles on Crabb, (1967-1969) (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - News articles on Crabb, (1970-1972) (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - Writings about Crabb’s work. (Box 68, Folder 13)
- Reviews from Newspapers, (1942-1957)
  - Newspaper reviews, (1942) (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper reviews, (1943-1944) (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper reviews, (1945) (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper reviews, (1946-47) (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper reviews, (1948) (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper reviews, (1949) (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper reviews, (1950-1951) (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper reviews, (1952) (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper reviews, (1953-1954) (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper reviews, (1955) (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper reviews, (1956) (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper reviews, (1957) (Box 69, Folder 12)
- Radio Scripts
  - Radio script (Lewis & Clark Expedition) (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Radio script (College series: University of Texas Longhorns) (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Radio script(College series: Texas Agricultural & Mechanical College ) (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Radio script (College series: University of Oklahoma), 1933 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Radio script (College series: University of Oklahoma), 1933 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Radio Script (Broadcast by the State Teachers College), 1935-1937 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Radio Script (State Teachers College East Radford), 1937 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Lewis And Clark Expedition (Box 70, Folder 8)
- Certificates of Appreciation and Special Extracts
  - Kiwanis Club of Nashville Certificates (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - An Ode to Dr. Alfred Leland Crabb. (State of Tennessee) (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - A .L. Crabb State of Tennessee: The senate Joint Resolution No. 189 By Senator Henry (Original triplicates) (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Extracts on Dinner at Belmont, Supper at the Maxwell house and Breakfast at the Hermitage (Box 71, Folder 4)
- Photographs (1)
  - Crabb File Pictures (1) (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Crabb File Pictures (2) (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Crabb File Pictures (3) (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Crabb File Pictures (4) (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Crabb File Pictures (5) (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Crabb File Pictures (6) (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Crabb File Pictures (7) (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Crabb File Pictures (8) (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Crabb File Pictures (9) (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Crabb File Pictures (10) (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Crabb File Pictures (11) (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Crabb File Pictures (12) (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Crabb File Pictures (13) (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Crabb File Pictures (14) (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - Crabb File Pictures (15) (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - Crabb File Pictures (16) (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - Crabb File Pictures (17) (Box 72, Folder 17)
  - Crabb File Pictures (18) (Box 72, Folder 18)
  - Crabb File Pictures (19) (Box 72, Folder 19)
  - Crabb File Pictures (20) (Box 72, Folder 20)
  - Crabb File Pictures (22) (Box 72, Folder 21)
  - Crabb File Pictures (23) (Box 72, Folder 22)
  - Crabb File Pictures (24) (Box 72, Folder 23)
- Photographs (2)
  - Crabb File Pictures (1) (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Crabb File Pictures (2) (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Crabb File Pictures (3) (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Crabb File Pictures (4) (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Crabb File Pictures (5) (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Crabb File Pictures (6) (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Crabb File Pictures (7) (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Crabb File Pictures (8) (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Crabb File Pictures (9) (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Crabb File Pictures (10) (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Crabb File Pictures (11) (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Crabb File Pictures (12) (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Crabb File Pictures (13) (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Crabb File Pictures (14) (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Crabb File Pictures (15) (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Crabb File Pictures (16) (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - Crabb File Pictures (17) (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Crabb File Pictures (18) (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Crabb File Pictures (19) (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - Crabb File Pictures (20) (Box 73, Folder 20)
- Scrapbook and Personal Newspaper Clippings
  - Scrapbook and A. L. Crabb (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Personal Clipping Extracts (Box 74, Folder 2)
- Obituary Certificates and Writings
  - Children’s Literature (1) (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Children’s Literature (2) (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Membership And Certificates (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Teaching Class Activities (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - The Cumberland River (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Creative Writing (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Certificates and Honors (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - The Round Table, (1884-1931) (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Obituary of A. L. Crabb and Family. (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Old Family Documents (Family letters and research) (Box 75, Folder 10)